inta.org 2003-04-02

# INTA | Privacy Policy

By using the INTA site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the INTA site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes.

**_Our Commitment_**

The International Trademark Association (“INTA”) respects your concern about privacy. This privacy policy will tell you how we protect your personal information, and will describe the choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer to this policy regularly.

**_Online Information Gathering_**

**Types of information collected by this site:** Information collected online is often defined as being either personally identifiable or anonymous:

  * **_Personally Identifiable Information_**  
Lets us know the specifics of who you are, such as your name, e-mail address or postal address.
  *  ** _Anonymous Information_**  
Is information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

The choice of how much of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to INTA is left completely up to you.

The only way we know something about you is when you use a personalized service, such as the “Members Only” area or the TMtopics e-mail discussion list, or you voluntarily disclose your information such as a credit card number, address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address, demographic, and other personal and financial information when you transact business at our site, communicate on the site by sending us an e-mail, or fill in a form.

In some cases, such as on our list services, discussion boards, or other forums, any personal information provided may become publicly available to our members and possibly the larger general public. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose such personal information (e.g. user name and e-mail address as used in a signature line), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties.

**Please note that if you are an active member of INTA, you may have been assigned a membership id and password to be used for accessing the “Members Only” area of our site. This information is maintained by INTA and is used solely to allow you to access the “Members Only” area**.

**Collection of IP addresses:** When visiting any Internet site your unique address, called an “IP address”, is recorded. The amount of information about users made available from their IP addresses varies greatly, for instance depending on how they are connected to the Internet. INTA does not release any information about the collection of this address to any third parties. INTA archives the logging of IP addresses for security reasons.

**Anonymous Information:**

INTA collects and archives basic logging for site stats. These log files show the daily number of visitors to our site and its subdirectories, the daily requests we receive for particular files, what server locations those requests come from, including from which countries, as well as the domain name of the server or browser accessing the INTA site. These aggregated statistics are primarily used internally to provide better service to the public, but may also be provided to others.

**_Non-disclosure_**

INTA does not sell, rent, lend or give personally identifiable information collected from you on INTA’s web site to marketers. **The one exception** is that, although unlikely, INTA may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information. In these cases, we will provide this information as and to the extent we have determined that the disclosure of any such information is appropriate.

**_Cookies_**

To enable any shopping features that may be available or become available on the INTA web site, our server will assign your browser a unique identification number stored in a file on your computer (a “cookie”). Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. This unique identification number will automatically identify your browser to our computers whenever you interact on our site.

**_Links_**

Users will find links to other sites or services on the INTA site. Although we initially visit the sites or services that are linked to INTA’s web site, we do not control the content or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. The fact that we have made these links available to you is not an endorsement or recommendation to you by INTA. We provide these links only as a convenience. For more information please see  The INTA Web Site Linking Policy.

Other companies linked to this site may collect information about you when you view or click on these sites. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these content providers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies, or no policy at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.
